designerevaluation.com 2015-02-08

# Privacy Policy – Designer Evaluation

We are committed to protect and respect your privacy. This policy sets out the basis on which personal data we are collecting from you will be processed. Please read the following to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and ways we use to treat it. The visit on this website along with electronic communication confirms your consent to process and transfer your personal data as set in this Privacy Policy.

## Collecting Personal Information

You may select to place orders using the website or receive additional information or services from us. When you place orders or request additional information regarding your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and payment details,we may ask for demographic information to enable us to provide a personalized service. The information is either manual or electronically stored in our databases.

## Using Personal Data

We will use your personal data to fulfill your requests while asking for data that is appropriate, relevant, and moderate for such purposes. When we ask you for personal data, it may include the following reasons:

  * We may communicate you occasionally to inform you about new products and services
  * We may send you consistent updates on issues we consider of your interest
  * We may send you requested information on our products and services
  * We may use your personal data for marketing purposes along with market research
  * We may use your personal data for internal purposes to administer this website, which may enable us to improve our services

## Unsubscribe

We anticipate that you will be happy with our services. If you do not wish to receive emails from us and want to be removed from our mailing list, you can select "unsubscribe" from any of the marketing emails we send or contact us.

## Anonymous Data Collection

Along with the information we gather as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information regarding use of our website. Our web server automatically logs the pages of our website to you or visitors view, their IP addresses along with the use of web browsers. This technology does not identify personal information but it simply enables us to compile statistics regarding our visitors and their use of our website.

## Cookies

For gathering anonymous information, we may use cookies that remain in the cookies file of your browser until it is closed. These cookies cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser and stored on your hard drive of computer. You can set your browser to notify you on receiving a cookie. We also use your IP address to diagnose issues with our service and administer it as well. The IP address is also used for determining your domain to gauge demographics of our users.

## Disclosing of Personal Data

We do not share, sell, or rent your personal data with irrelevant third parties except provided in this Privacy Policy and under these situations:

  * For providing you with the information or products you have requested, your data may be transferred or shared with companies or third parties processing according to the purpose of collecting data or for the purpose you have consented.
  * We will maintain your contact details on our database and may post you information to make you aware of our similar products and services that may be of your interest.

## Data Access and Corrections

Upon receiving of your request and sufficient information to permit us to identify your personal information, we will disclose you the data we hold about you. We will correct, modify, or delete any personal information that is not accurate and you may update any information you have provided us by contacting through contact us or cusotmer support.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be updated on this page.
